<resources>
    <string name="app_name">RecyclerView</string>
    <string name="caesar">Ingredients:
green salad – 1 bunch;
chicken – 300 grams;
tomato – 1 piece;
Parmesan cheese – 200 grams;
garlic – 1 clove;
white bread – 4 slices;
butter – 50 grams;
salt.
Method of preparation
Lettuce rinse under running water, dry them and put in the fridge.
Chicken fillet wash and cut into small thin slices.
In a pan melt half of butter. When it is hot, add 2-3 cloves of garlic, cut into small pieces. Stir and put in a bowl the pieces of meat. Fry until Golden brown. Ready to put the slices in a bowl.
In a pan again heat the remaining oil with the garlic cloves. White bread cut into small squares and fry. Stir it continuously so that the croutons do not burn.
In a large pot finely to pick some salad leaves, add the chicken, diced tomato and grated as finely as possible Parmesan. All the ingredients mix well. On top lay the crackers.
If "Caesar" will seem dry, it can be refilled with a mixture of mustard, egg yolk and lemon juice.
Bon appetit!</string>
    <string name="dumplings">Ingredients:
wheat flour – 1.5 cups;
water – 1 glass;
pork – 250 grams;
beef – 250 grams;
garlic – 1 clove;
onion – 1 piece;
black pepper, salt;
milk – 0.5 cups.
Method of preparation
The most delicious dumplings out of dough in the boiling water.
Boil the water and pour a Cup of boiling water in a deep bowl. Add a teaspoon of salt and slowly add pre-sifted through a sieve flour. Knead by hand a soft dough.
A wooden Board dusted with flour and knead the dough until it stops sticking to your hands. Roll into a ball, cover with a towel made of natural fabrics and give 20 minutes to stand up.
During this time prepare the meat filling. Through a meat grinder to crank out beef and pork, and then again with onion and garlic. Received minced salt and pepper pritrusit. All the ingredients are thoroughly mixed.
In the bowl of stuffing to pour so much milk that it was not too thick, but did not spread.
The rested dough is divided into 4 parts. Roll out long "sausages". Each divided into 15 parts and roll it out thinly. In the middle, ready to put the stuffing and sumipntg edge. Tips to keep each other and a good squeeze, giving the classic dumpling shape.
Boil water and put the first batch of products in the boiling water. Cook for 6-8 minutes on high heat. Serves homemade dumplings with butter and sour cream.
Bon appetit!</string>
    <string name="pizza">For the dough will need 250 ml of water, 15 grams or 2 teaspoons of fresh dry yeast, 400 grams of flour, 1 teaspoon salt and 2 tablespoons of olive oil. Of all these ingredients and knead soft dough and let him lie down for 15 minutes. For the toppings 3 sausage cut into slices, 1 bell pepper – strips, 3-4 tomatoes – sliced no thicker than 4 mm, 150 grams of cheese to grate. The amount of cheese can be adjusted depending on your preferences, it will never be a lot.

Divide the dough into 3 equal parts. One of them stretched until, until it will cover the entire form, while the edges need to form ledges. They need to ensure that the filling doesn\'t run out for inside the future of pizza. The dough is smeared with two tablespoons of tomato sauce and mayonnaise. Then on the form spread some cheese all chopped and sliced sausage. Bell peppers and tomatoes to try to distribute evenly on the surface. The top layer will be cheese ball, which abundantly cover the form.

The oven should turn on the pre, holding the highest possible temperature. Baked the pizza for about 10 minutes, until the cheese will have a beautiful crust. In the case of using picsearch mode is selected "two ten", and the cooking time will be billed in 8 minutes. When the dish is ready, it is cut into pieces and eat hot. A traditional pizza recipe is simple, but at the same time universal. The taste of Italian pizza will please everyone and will certainly be tempted to try another piece.</string>
    <string name="chicken">"In the 1940's, Colonel Sanders developed the original recipe chicken to be sold at his gas station diner. At the time, the recipe was written above the door so anyone could have read it. But today, we go to great lengths to protect such a sacred blend of herbs and spices. In fact, the recipe ranks among America's most valuable trade secrets."</string>
    <string name="kebab">To prepare the marinade for 1 kg of meat 3 onions, salt, black pepper or mixture of peppers, 3 tablespoons Apple cider, wine vinegar or lemon juice. Cut onion rings and mixed with other ingredients, then add the marinade to the meat. Stand the mixture from 5 hours to one day. A convenient container for marinating meat will be a few plastic bags that are nested in each other. Absolutely can not put the product into aluminum cookware.
Put marinated meat on skewers, alternating with onion rings, or put on the grill. Cook it about 15-20 minutes over hot coals, turning occasionally. Serve the kebab with ketchup, mustard, vegetables, lemon wedges. A classic kebab recipe will delight your taste and unsurpassed flavor of any gourmet.</string>
</resources>
